germanbarngirls.com 2011-01-18

# germanbarngirls.com -Our Commitment To Privacy

PRIVACY POLICY

We are aware that you care how your personal information is used and shared. We are absolutely committed to preserving your privacy rights and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. Therefore, to the extent our Site collects any information from you at all, we want you to fully understand and agree to what is done with it. We have tried to include a link to this policy on every page on which personal information is collected. And please remember, if you ever have any questions at all about privacy concerns, we invite you to contact us directly at: [cs@germanbarngirls.com](mailto:cs@germanbarngirls.com)

Use

This is an Adult Site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. This Site does not seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18 or under the age of majority in the jurisdiction you reside in and from which you access the Site. All such underage persons are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents on this Site without exception. If you are underage, your account will be terminated without notice or delay.

Consent 

By using this Site and/or volunteering information you are giving your express consent to the Site's Privacy Policy as outlined in this document. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Site.

What We Collect 

"Personally identifiable information" is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, e-mail address, home or work address, telephone number or payment information. We only have access to the personally identifiable information that you provide to us. For example, we cannot determine your e-mail address unless you provide it. We cannot gain access to other information on your computer. Those who visit only public areas of the Site and who do not purchase goods or services do not need to, and generally do not, provide us with any personally identifiable information. Those who wish to join the Site, however, or to purchase products or services from us or from third parties offering their goods, content and/or services through us, must provide us with enough information to enable us or our affiliates to process the requested transaction, including your payment information, credit card information and the like. This generally includes, at a minimum, personally identifiable information such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. If you become a Member, you also will have a username and password combination. Once you register and log in to the member area, you are no longer anonymous to us. We may also collect referring Website and browser information and other related data.

Security and Access

We use a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access. You can access Your Account from within the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit card information, mailing list preferences, and services requested.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. However, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

Storage of Personal Information

All personal information and credit card information will be stored in databases hosted by Alreston Investments Limited in Cyprus and by the third party service providers with whom you have authorized us to share your information. These third party providers will receive some or all of your personal information in order to fulfill your service requests.

Do We Share the Information We Gather?

Information about our users is an important part of our business and we take steps to maintain the privacy and security of such information against unauthorized access. We generally use such information for such purposes as customizing future user experiences, improving our services, and communicating with you if you have authorized such communication. If you have joined a "Free" Site of ours that offers you free access to our Site and Services in exchange for your Opt-in to a co-registration agreement, we will share your personal information with the other third party affiliated adult sites shown at the time you join; age verification services who receive necessary information from us in order to verify your age and identity; and credit, debit and cash transaction providers who receive necessary information from the third party providers in order for you to pay for your memberships if you join their sites. We do this in order to allow a transaction of yours to occur if you determine to join those sites beyond any free access or limited free membership period and to provide you with an account and services. If you have any issues with sharing this information or would like further information about them, please contact us via email at [cs@germanbarngirls.com](mailto:cs@germanbarngirls.com).

In an effort to serve you better and improve your online experience, we may also share such information as described below.

  * Aggregated Research Data

We produce research reports and other data about our transactions. Such data is based upon aggregated, anonymous information about hundreds of thousands of users and does not include personally identifiable information about individuals.

  * Agents 

From time to time, we employ other companies and individuals to perform various functions on our behalf. Examples include, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results, processing credit card payments, providing customer service, and reducing fraud. They have access to that information that we collect that is needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

  * Special Offers

Sometimes, we send offers to selected customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name or address. We send the offer directly to those customers and control the information used to make the offer and do not share the list or any information about our customers with the other business. However, please understand that if you do receive this type of information from us and choose to take advantage of it, the other business may then learn information about you because only customers with certain characteristics may have received the offer.

There are, however, circumstances in which we may share the information we collect about you (as described above) with other companies in order to provide you with access to products and services and to serve you effectively. We require these companies to adhere to our privacy standards and to use this information only for the limited purpose for which it was shared. We do not allow them to disclose it to others without prior approval.

Third Party Links from our Site

Third Party service providers may have advertising banners and/or links on our Site. Naturally, we are not responsible for the use of any information that you may provide, or that is gathered by third-parties that have banner ads or links on our Site, because we do not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any third-parties. Whenever applicable, you should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on our Site. 

"Opt-In" & "Opt-Out"

Some offers found on this Site may be presented to you with the option to express your preference by either clicking or entering "accept" or "yes" or "decline" or "no". If you select "accept" or "yes" you are saying that you "Opt-In" to the offer and agree that your personal information and data may be disclosed to third parties. Other offers may be presented with a pre-selected preference of choice. If you do not deselect the pre-selected preference (i.e. "Opt-Out") then we may transfer your personal information to the third party making the offer. If you do deselect the preference then no personal information will be disclosed.

Other Corporate Entities

We share much of our data with our subsidiaries and joint ventures that are committed to serving you throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our subsidiaries and joint ventures follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law.

Business Transactions

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise as described above). Also, in the unlikely event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

Protection of Us and Others

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; assist in fraud protection or investigation; or protect the rights, property, or security of us, our users, or others. We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws. Therefore, in response to a verified and legitimate request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, e-mail address and other information without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and comply with our obligation as a good corporate citizen, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or report suspected illegal activity.

Due to the existing regulatory and legal environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be required to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

By providing your personal information to this Site, you are expressly consenting to the use and disclosure of your personal information by the Site for the purposes stated above and in the manner that it sees fit.

Review of Personal Information by you/Means of Challenging Data

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy or if you feel that the personal information is inaccurate or incomplete, you may e-mail the Site's Data Controller at [cs@germanbarngirls.com](mailto:cs@germanbarngirls.com). The Data Controller has the authority to resolve all issues regarding the collection, modification, correction, deletion and use of the personal information that has been collected by the Site.

Changes to this Policy

From time to time, this Site may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our practices change, we will post the policy changes to this Site to notify you of these changes. It is your responsibility to review these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please contact the Data Controller by e-mail at [cs@germanbarngirls.com](mailto:cs@germanbarngirls.com). Above all, you alone are responsible for keeping your information safe. Be careful and responsible whenever you access a Website.

Terms and Conditions of Membership

You must carefully read each of the terms and conditions of membership for this Site. By accepting membership to this Site, you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this Site to use your information.

Ownership

This Site is owned and operated by Alreston Investments Ltd. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or if you feel that we are not following the stated Policy, you may contact us by: 

Mail: Alreston Investments Ltd.  
10 Kolokotroni Street  
Flat 101   
Strovolos, Nicosia,   
2063   
Cyprus 

Email: [cs@germanbarngirls.com](mailto:cs@germanbarngirls.com)

Facsimile: _______________  
Last Updated: 02/20/2010
